A Guide to the Virginia Housing Study Commission Records, 1970-2004
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Correspondence and Subject Files (Assistant, Nancy Blanchard), 1971-2004., Extent: 4 cubic feet. (Box 16-19.)
  - HB 625, undated. (Box 17)
  - HB 933 and HB 1083, undated. (Box 16)
  - HB 1145 (Housing Authorities), 2000. (Box 16)
  - HB 1251, undated. (Box 17)
  - HB 1322, undated. (Box 17)
  - HB 1513, undated. (Box 17)
  - HB 2453 (Condemnation), 1997. (Box 17)
  - HB 2471 (Virginia Mortgage Lending Act), undated. (Box 16)
  - HJR 8, undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 161, undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 181, undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 208, 1998. (Box 17)
  - HJR 236 (USBC), undated. (Box 12, 16)
  - HJR 241, undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 253 (Carbon Monoxide), undated. (Box 16)
  - HJR 254/SJR 446 (Home Ownership), 2002. (Box 16)
  - HJR 256 (Indoor Plumbing), undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 257 (Rural Housing), undated. (Box 16)
  - HJR 438, undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 489, undated. (Box >17)
  - HJR 554, 1997. (Box 17)
  - HJR 619 (Eminent Domain), undated. (Box 16)
  - HJR 619 (Housing Authorities), 2001. (Box 16)
  - HJR 620 (New Building Products), 2002. (Box 16)
  - HJR 739 (VRL and T)/HB 145, undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 744, undated. (Box 17)
  - HJR 747, 1999. (Box 17)
  - HJR 760, undated. (Box 17)
  - Housing Partnership Fund, undated. (Box 18)
  - Interim Meeting (Binder), 2001. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1990. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1992. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1993. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1994. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1995. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1996. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1997. (Box 18)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1998. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 1999. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Meeting (Binder), 2000. (Box 19)
  - Legislative Summary, 1994-2000. (Box 16)
  - Legislative Work Session, 1998. (Box 16)
  - Mold and Mildew, undated. (Box 16)
  - Mortgage Lending Practices, undated. (Box 17)
  - Public Hearings, 1994. (Box 16)
  - Public Hearings, 1995. (Box 16)
  - Real Property Issues, Subcommittee on, 1997. (Box 17)
  - Richlands Public Housing, 1995. (Box 17)
  - Richmond Public Housing, 1995-1996. (Box 17)
  - SB 97, undated. (Box 17)
  - SB 266 and SB 267, undated. (Box 17)
  - SB 520, undated. (Box 17)
  - SJR 111 (Fair Housing), 2002. (Box 16)
  - SJR 115, 1998. (Box 17)
  - SJR 347, undated. (Box 17)
  - SJR ? (Affordable Housing/Manufacturing Needs), undated. (Box 16)
  - State Fire Marshall, undated. (Box 17)
  - Statewide Housing Policy, undated. (Box 16)
  - Study Agenda, 1994-2000. (Box 16)
  - Unexpensed Fiscal Balance, 2002 FY. (Box 18)
  - VACDC, undated. (Box 18)
  - VIACH, 2000-2001. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Constitution, undated. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Foundation, undated. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Partnership Fund Ad Hoc Advisory, undated. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Study Commission, History of, 1971-1982. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Study Commission Master File, undated. (Box 18)
  - Visitability, 2003. (Box 16)
  - Wintergreen Notebooks (Printing), undated. (Box 16)
  - Work Session, 1999-2002. (Box 16)